<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Code Musings]]></title><description><![CDATA[A place for me to discuss code and the things I am loving in web development]]></description><link>https://aerivas.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 07:04:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Code Musings Chapter 01]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to Code Musings, the ramblings and musings of a designer, turned developer and teacher. This blog will center on the things that I…]]></description><link>https://aerivas.com/code-musings-ch-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://aerivas.com/code-musings-ch-01/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Code Musings, the ramblings and musings of a designer, turned developer and teacher.&lt;br&gt;
This blog will center on the things that I am learning and growing in at any given time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that while I hope to share many good ideas AND good code. There is a distinct possibility that at some point I will get it wrong. This is all part of the learning process and growth process. I will do my best to keep things updated as I continue learning, and will release update blogs if I think the issue is big enough to warrant talking about more in depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early on in the blog I will likely be talking a lot about Angular, c#.net, and core web things. But I hope that in time I will cover a wide variety of topics spanning everything from design to code. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may ask, “Why start with Angular and c#.net?” At the core, the topics on this blog will cover whatever is relevant to me at the time, and as I start this blog my job centers on these technologies. And to be clear, I am still pretty new to both of these pieces of tech, so go easy on me and come along for this learning journey and ride. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to learning and growing with all of my readers (That’s you!). I hope you enjoy it, but maybe more importantly I hope you learn something.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>